Tufts Dental Outlook UP050
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Tufts Dental Outlook
1928 -- 1992
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
School of Dental Medicine
UP050
0.5 Linear Feet
10 Volumes
Arrangement
This collection is organized in one series.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains issues of Tufts Dental Outlook, published by students of the Tufts University School of Dental Medicine. Tufts Dental Outlook ceased publication in the 1970s and resumed publication in the early 1980s. It contains bimonthly issues from 1928-55, thereafter quarterly until the 1980s.
Biographical / Historical
Tufts University School of Dental Medicine was established in 1868 as Boston Dental College. It was incorporated into Tufts College in 1899. Although founded as a school to educate students from New England, today Tufts is renowned throughout the United States and the world as a center for academic and clinical excellence. Tufts boasts over 6,900 alumni composed of individuals from all fifty states and thirty-nine countries. The majority of the alumni outside of the USA have completed an Advanced Education Certificate program. Students receive a comprehensive education emphasizing the importance of didactic coursework, clinical experience, and practice management that prepares them to enter the work force as confident, proficient clinicians.
- Tufts Dental Outlook, 1928 -- 1992; UP050.001; 0.5 Linear Feet; 10 Volumes
  Scope and Contents
  Tufts Dental Outlook is published by students of the Tufts University School of Dental Medicine. Tufts Dental Outlook ceased publication in the 1970s and resumed publication in the early 1980s.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1928-05; UP050.001.001.00001 (Box Volume 1)
    Volume, issue
    1, 1
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1928-12; UP050.001.001.00002 (Box Volume 1)
    2, 1
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1929-02; UP050.001.001.00003 (Box Volume 1)
    2, 2
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1929-02; UP050.001.001.00004 (Box Volume 1)
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1929-04; UP050.001.001.00005 (Box Volume 1)
    2, 3
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1929-11; UP050.001.001.00006 (Box Volume 1)
    3, 1
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1930-01; UP050.001.001.00007 (Box Volume 1)
    3, 2
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1930-03; UP050.001.001.00008 (Box Volume 1)
    3, 3
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1930-05; UP050.001.001.00009 (Box Volume 1)
    3, 4
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1930-11; UP050.001.001.00010 (Box Volume 1)
    4, 1
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1930-02; UP050.001.001.00011 (Box Volume 1)
    4, 2
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1931-04; UP050.001.001.00012 (Box Volume 1)
    4, 3
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1931-06; UP050.001.001.00013 (Box Volume 1)
    4, 4
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1931-12; UP050.001.001.00014 (Box Volume 1)
    4, 5
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1932-03; UP050.001.001.00015 (Box Volume 1)
    5, 2
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1932-05; UP050.001.001.00016 (Box Volume 1)
    5, 3
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1932-10; UP050.001.001.00017 (Box Volume 1)
    6, 1
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1933-01; UP050.001.001.00018 (Box Volume 1)
    6, 2
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1933-03; UP050.001.001.00019 (Box Volume 1)
    7, 1
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1933-05; UP050.001.001.00020 (Box Volume 1)
    7, 2
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1933-11; UP050.001.001.00021 (Box Volume 1)
    7, 3
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1934-02; UP050.001.001.00022 (Box Volume 1)
    7, 4
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1934-03; UP050.001.002.00001 (Box Volume 2)
    8, 1
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1934-05; UP050.001.002.00002 (Box Volume 2)
    8, 2
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1934-11; UP050.001.002.00003 (Box Volume 2)
    8, 3
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1935-01; UP050.001.002.00004 (Box Volume 2)
    8, 4
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1935-03; UP050.001.002.00005 (Box Volume 2)
    9, 1
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1935-05; UP050.001.002.00006 (Box Volume 2)
    9, 2
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1935-05; UP050.001.002.00007 (Box Volume 2)
    9, 3
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1936-02; UP050.001.002.00008 (Box Volume 2)
    9, 4
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1936-04; UP050.001.002.00009 (Box Volume 2)
    10, 1
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1936-05; UP050.001.002.00010 (Box Volume 2)
    10, 2
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1936-11; UP050.001.002.00011 (Box Volume 2)
    10, 3
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1937-02; UP050.001.002.00012 (Box Volume 2)
    10, 4
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1937-04; UP050.001.002.00013 (Box Volume 2)
    11, 1
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1937-04; UP050.001.002.00014 (Box Volume 2)
    11, 2
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1937-11; UP050.001.002.00015 (Box Volume 2)
    11, 3
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1938-03; UP050.001.002.00016 (Box Volume 2)
    11, 4
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1938-05; UP050.001.003.00001 (Box Volume 3)
    12, 1
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1938-10; UP050.001.003.00002 (Box Volume 3)
    12, 2
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1939-02; UP050.001.003.00003 (Box Volume 3)
    12, 3
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1939-04; UP050.001.003.00004 (Box Volume 3)
    13, 1
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1939-11; UP050.001.003.00006 (Box Volume 3)
    13, 3
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1940-02; UP050.001.003.00007 (Box Volume 3)
    13, 4
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1940-04; UP050.001.003.00008 (Box Volume 3)
    14, 1
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1940-10; UP050.001.003.00009 (Box Volume 3)
    14, 2
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1941-01; UP050.001.003.00010 (Box Volume 3)
    14, 3
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1941-03; UP050.001.003.00011 (Box Volume 3)
    14, 4
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1941-05; UP050.001.004.00001 (Box Volume 4)
    15, 1
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1941-10; UP050.001.004.00002 (Box Volume 4)
    15, 2
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1942-01; UP050.001.004.00003 (Box Volume 4)
    15, 3
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1942-05; UP050.001.004.00004 (Box Volume 4)
    15, 4
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1942-05; UP050.001.004.00005 (Box Volume 4)
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1943-07; UP050.001.004.00006 (Box Volume 4)
    16, 1
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1942-10; UP050.001.004.00007 (Box Volume 4)
    16, 2
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1943-01; UP050.001.004.00008 (Box Volume 4)
    16, 3
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1943-04; UP050.001.004.00009 (Box Volume 4)
    16, 4
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1943-06; UP050.001.004.00010 (Box Volume 4)
    17, 1
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1943-09; UP050.001.004.00011 (Box Volume 4)
    17, 2
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1943-12; UP050.001.004.00012 (Box Volume 4)
    17, 3
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1944-03; UP050.001.004.00013 (Box Volume 4)
    18, 1
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1944-05; UP050.001.004.00014 (Box Volume 4)
    18, 2
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1944-08; UP050.001.004.00015 (Box Volume 4)
    18, 3
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1944-12; UP050.001.004.00016 (Box Volume 4)
    18, 4
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1945-03; UP050.001.005.00001 (Box Volume 5)
    19, 1
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1945-06; UP050.001.005.00002 (Box Volume 5)
    19, 2
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1945-10; UP050.001.005.00003 (Box Volume 5)
    19, 3
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1945-12; UP050.001.005.00004 (Box Volume 5)
    19, 4
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1946-03; UP050.001.005.00005 (Box Volume 5)
    20, 1
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1946-06; UP050.001.005.00006 (Box Volume 5)
    20, 2
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1946-10; UP050.001.005.00007 (Box Volume 5)
    20, 3
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1946-12; UP050.001.005.00008 (Box Volume 5)
    20, 4
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1946-04; UP050.001.005.00009 (Box Volume 5)
    21, 1
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1947-09; UP050.001.005.00010 (Box Volume 5)
    21, 2
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1948-02; UP050.001.005.00011 (Box Volume 5)
    21, 3
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1948-02; UP050.001.005.00012 (Box Volume 5)
    21, 4
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1948-11; UP050.001.006.00001 (Box Volume 6)
    22, 1
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1949-01; UP050.001.006.00002 (Box Volume 6)
    22, 2
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1949-05; UP050.001.006.00003 (Box Volume 6)
    22, 3
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1950-02; UP050.001.006.00005 (Box Volume 6)
    23, 2
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1950-04; UP050.001.006.00006 (Box Volume 6)
    23, 3
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1950-06; UP050.001.006.00007 (Box Volume 6)
    23, 4
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1951-02; UP050.001.006.00008 (Box Volume 6)
    24, 1
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1951-04; UP050.001.006.00009 (Box Volume 6)
    24, 2
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1952-03; UP050.001.006.00010 (Box Volume 6)
    25, 1
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1952-05; UP050.001.006.00011 (Box Volume 6)
    25, 2
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1952-11; UP050.001.006.00012 (Box Volume 6)
    25, 3
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1953-01; UP050.001.006.00013 (Box Volume 6)
    25, 4
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1953-03; UP050.001.007.00001 (Box Volume 7)
    26, 1
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1953-05; UP050.001.007.00002 (Box Volume 7)
    26, 2
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1953-11; UP050.001.007.00003 (Box Volume 7)
    26, 3
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1954-01; UP050.001.007.00004 (Box Volume 7)
    26, 4
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1954-04; UP050.001.007.00005 (Box Volume 7)
    27, 1
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1954-11; UP050.001.007.00006 (Box Volume 7)
    27, 3
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1955-02; UP050.001.007.00007 (Box Volume 7)
    27, 4
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1955-03; UP050.001.007.00008 (Box Volume 7)
    28, 1
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, 1955-06; UP050.001.007.00009 (Box Volume 7)
    28, 2
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, Fall, 1955; UP050.001.007.00010 (Box Volume 7)
    28, 3
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, Winter, 1956; UP050.001.007.00011 (Box Volume 7)
    28, 4
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, Spring, 1956; UP050.001.008.00001 (Box Volume 8)
    29, 1
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, Summer, 1956; UP050.001.008.00002 (Box Volume 8)
    29, 2
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, Fall, 1956; UP050.001.008.00003 (Box Volume 8)
    29, 3
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, Winter, 1956; UP050.001.008.00004 (Box Volume 8)
    29, 4
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, Spring, 1957; UP050.001.008.00005 (Box Volume 8)
    30, 1
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, Summer, 1957; UP050.001.008.00006 (Box Volume 8)
    30, 2
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, Fall, 1957; UP050.001.008.00007 (Box Volume 8)
    30, 3
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, Winter, 1957; UP050.001.008.00008 (Box Volume 8)
    30, 4
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, Spring, 1958; UP050.001.008.00009 (Box Volume 8)
    31, 1
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, Summer, 1958; UP050.001.008.00010 (Box Volume 8)
    31, 2
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, Fall, 1958; UP050.001.008.00011 (Box Volume 8)
    31, 3
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, Winter, 1958; UP050.001.008.00012 (Box Volume 8)
    31, 4
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, Fall, 1960; UP050.001.009.00001 (Box Volume 9)
    33, 1
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, Winter, 1960; UP050.001.009.00002 (Box Volume 9)
    33, 2
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, Spring, 1961; UP050.001.009.00003 (Box Volume 9)
    33, 3
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, Fall, 1961; UP050.001.009.00004 (Box Volume 9)
    33, 4
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, Winter, 1962; UP050.001.009.00005 (Box Volume 9)
    34, 1
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, Spring, 1962; UP050.001.009.00006 (Box Volume 9)
    34, 2
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, Summer, 1962; UP050.001.009.00007 (Box Volume 9)
    34, 3
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, Fall, 1962; UP050.001.009.00008 (Box Volume 9)
    34, 4
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, Winter, 1963; UP050.001.010.00001 (Box Volume 10)
    35, 1
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, Spring, 1963; UP050.001.010.00002 (Box Volume 10)
    35, 2
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, Summer, 1963; UP050.001.010.00003 (Box Volume 10)
    35, 3
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, Winter, 1964; UP050.001.010.00004 (Box Volume 10)
    36, 1
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, Spring, 1964; UP050.001.010.00005 (Box Volume 10)
    36, 2
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, Summer-Fall, 1964; UP050.001.010.00006 (Box Volume 10)
    36, 3
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, Fall-Winter, 1964 -- 1965; UP050.001.010.00007 (Box Volume 10)
    Vol.36 No.4-Vol.37 No. 1
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, Fall, 1959; UP050.001.011.00001 (Box 11)
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, Winter and Summer, 1960; UP050.001.011.00002 (Box 11)
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, Spring, 1965; UP050.001.011.00003 (Box 11)
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, Summer, 1967; UP050.001.011.00004 (Box 11)
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, Winter, Spring, and Fall, 1968; UP050.001.011.00005 (Box 11)
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, Winter, 1969; UP050.001.011.00006 (Box 11)
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, Spring, 1970; UP050.001.011.00007 (Box 11)
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, May, 1980; UP050.001.011.00008 (Box 11)
    From disbound volume.
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, Spring, 1981; UP050.001.011.00009 (Box 11)
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, Summer/Fall, 1983; UP050.001.011.00010 (Box 11)
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, September, 1984; UP050.001.011.00011 (Box 11)
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, February, 1986; UP050.001.011.00012 (Box 11)
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, Autumn, 1988; UP050.001.011.00013 (Box 11)
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, Winter, 1989 -- 1990; UP050.001.011.00014 (Box 11)
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, Summer, 1991; UP050.001.011.00015 (Box 11)
  - Tufts Dental Outlook, Summer, 1992; UP050.001.011.00016 (Box 11)